http://www.smartfurniture.com/privacy.html

We Protect Your Privacy
As people who regularly shop online, we know how important it is to keep your personal information confidential, especially online. Our commitment to protecting your privacy is outlined in the policies below. This Privacy Policy was created to inform you what information we collect when you visit SmartFurniture.com (referred to as the "Site" "SmartFurniture.com", or "our website") and then how that information is collected and used by us.
Overview
First off, it is important that you know we are serious about protecting your privacy and protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. The personal information you provide us is used for processing your order, and customizing your shopping experience. Under no circumstances will we share your personal details with any other entity or third-party unless it relates specifically to providing you with the products or services you requested from us. We may use the information we collect to notify you about new products, events, or special offers. If you have any questions or comments concerning your privacy? Please feel free to contact us at marketing@smartfurniture.com. We read every email that we receive and will reply as quickly as we can.
What Customer Information Does SmartFurniture.com Collect?
We receive and store information you provide on our website. You may choose not to provide certain personal information; however, it may limit our ability to provide you with the best possible customer experience. We use your information to respond to information requests, to provide you with the products or services you requested, to provide you with a personal shopping experience, and to communicate with you. SmartFurniture.com is the owner of all information collected on this site.
We have not and do not plan to sell or rent any of our customers or prospects personally-identifiable information to any unrelated third party. Provided, however, in the event we merge with another company or sell our stock or assets to a third party, it is possible that our customers' information would be included in such a transaction. Except as expressly provided in this policy, we will not share your personal details with any other entity or third-party unless it relates to providing you with the information, products or services you requested from us or otherwise to provide you with a better shopping experience.
Our website uses web forms through which you may provide us with information, such as your name, addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and pertinent financial information. SmartFurniture.com collects this information and will use this information to provide the products, materials or services you request, and to send you promotional and news oriented information.
We collect demographic and profile data. We use this data to enhance your shopping experiences at SmartFurniture.com. We will also use this data to provide you with information which we believe you may have interest in, and to display website content according to what we determine you will prefer.
What About Cookies and IP Addresses?
SmartFurniture.com uses your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, to manage our website, to identify you and your shopping cart and to gather general demographic information. We use browser cookies to keep track of the contents of your shopping cart and for other purposes including site personalization. Should you set your browser to reject cookies, the site will not be able to recognize your cart, your account, or any personalization.
How Secure Is My Personal Information?
This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions through this Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate. For example, when you visit our Site, you access servers that are kept in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline.
Updates to this Policy
If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated.
Copyright 2015 by Smart Furniture, Inc. All rights reserved.
Share Via Email
THANK YOU!
Your Email has been sent.
Icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY
Icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY
Icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY
Icons made by Smashicons from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY
